<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on JuHye Mun</title>
    <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on JuHye Mun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 21:48:03 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 9</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 21:48:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-9/</guid>
      <description>Week 9 BLE: LED on/off control This week, I programmed my Huzzah board to respond to a BLE connection. I downloaded the BLE Scanner app by Bluepixel Technologies onto my iPhone.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the product looked like:   Here&amp;rsquo;s my code as a code snippet. (Code snippets in markdown can be embedded with 3 backward ticks):
/* Based on Neil Kolban example for IDF: https://github.com/nkolban/esp32-snippets/blob/master/cpp_utils/tests/BLE%20Tests/SampleWrite.cpp Ported to Arduino ESP32 by Evandro Copercini */ #include &amp;lt;BLEDevice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 4</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 21:48:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week4/</guid>
      <description>Week 4: Microcontroller Programming This week, I created a simple button-controlled music player!
Materials I used the M0 Metro Circuit from Adafruit, a piezo speaker, a button, and the breadboard from the PS 70 kit to start.
I first used the button circuit from class as inspiration. I attached a button and a resistor from ground to one of its legs. Then I connected this leg to digital input 8 so that I can program the button&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week3</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 21:48:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week3/</guid>
      <description>Week 3: Kinetic Sculpture This week, I created a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day themed rotating bird as a kinetic sculpture. This was definitely a journey &amp;ndash; it evolved into something much more fun that I anticipated!
Materials I used the M0 Metro Circuit from Adafruit, a potentiometer, a moter, and the breadboard from the PS 70 kit to start. Circuit inspired by class:  Circuit 
Attached the motor to the lego wheels and 3D printed structures from the hardware packet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 15:42:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-2/</guid>
      <description>Press Fit Construction Kit For this assignment, I collaborated with Hugh and Amy to create a cardboard press-fit kit for lampshades. I got this idea from a beautiful wooden lamp that I had seen on the internet:
 Photo from google images 
I realized that none of us were artists, and so we decided to create geometric patterns that would create a &amp;ldquo;starlight&amp;rdquo; effect over a lightbulb, like these:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PS 70 Project Proposal</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 17:41:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/proposal/</guid>
      <description>For my final project, I aim to build a midi controller where a person can change instrument sounds just by holding their hand up or horizontally or down. Because of the &amp;ldquo;hands off&amp;rdquo; concept, the musician/producer doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to rely on a bulky piece of hardware. The project could incorporate different sensors such as light, movement, and visual sensors (such as a camera). This product would simulate a two-dimensional plane, where each axis represents some customizable parameter to an instrument.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 5</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-5/</guid>
      <description>Week 5: 3D This week, I started an motion sensored alarm watch model.
Fusion 360 This model is inspired by the Apple Watch wrist band that ibudman! created.
Here, I used components from the PS70 kit, and imported them into my watch file through the insert function in Fusion 360. I used the Arduino microcontroller, piezo buzzer, battery 5V, and the accelerometer gyroscope. The microcontroller would hold the program that would play the buzzer while the gyroscope was not detecting movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 6</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week-6/</guid>
      <description>Week 6: Sensors This week, I used an accelerometer to measure the XYZ location and the acceration of my breadboard!
Materials I used the M0 Metro Circuit from Adafruit, and an Adafruit lis3dh accelerometer from the ps70 kit.
I followed along this Adafruit Guide! at first in order to gain a better understanding of how this sensor works.
How It Works The Adafruit LIS3DH triple-Axis Accelerometer Breakout has three axis sensing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 7</title>
      <link>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juhye-m.github.io/ps70/posts/week7/</guid>
      <description>Week 7 I had many ideas this week The first one was to create a mic-sensor controlled led output that lit up when the sound threshold past a certain point. The other was to use the feather controller to build upon my project from a couple weeks ago with the piezo speaker and music! Finally, for section, I created this awesome webcam.
Mic sensor For this project, I knew that I needed to wire up the mic and the LED with the m0 microcontroller such that the microphone was the input and the LED light was the output.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
